const dataProfessional = [
    {
        question: "Labour act was introduce/founded in",
        optionA: "2038",
        optionB: "2048",
        optionC: "2043",
        optionD: "2053",
        correct: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the chairperson of Central Labour Advisory Board?",
        optionA: "Secretroy of ministry of labour",
        optionB: "Specialist of ministry of labour",
        optionC: "Director General, department of labour",
        optionD: "Labour minister",
        correct: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "In Nepal, which of the following act contains the provisions on health and safety of the workers?",
        optionA: "contract act",
        optionB: "indusrty act",
        optionC: "labour act",
        optionD: "all of the above",
        correct: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "According to labour act considering health condition is",
        optionA: "first aid after accident ",
        optionB: "safety on instrument and cloth",
        optionC: "education  and training",
        optionD: "none of the above",
        correct: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Maximum working hour for a labour per week should be  ",
        optionA: "42hr",
        optionB: "45hr",
        optionC: "48hr",
        optionD: "53hr",
        correct: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Workers are not allowed to work continous more then",
        optionA: "3hr",
        optionB: "5hr",
        optionC: "7hr",
        optionD: "4hr",
        correct: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "The space required for living the worker is 15mÂ³ with considering the maximum height of room above floor level.",
        optionA: "3 m",
        optionB: "3.5 m",
        optionC: "4 m",
        optionD: "5 m",
        correct: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not concerned with the authority of Engineers?",
        optionA: "good behavior with client",
        optionB: "conscious with his profession",
        optionC: "divulge the confidential matter",
        optionD: "express an opinion on engineering matter",
        correct: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Ethics is the science which deals with",
        optionA: "rightness of professional",
        optionB: "wrong of professional",
        optionC: "both (a) and  (b) of above",
        optionD: "none of the above",
        correct: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Profession is defined as",
        optionA: "systematic knowledge through specialized training",
        optionB: "synonym to job or occupation",
        optionC: "types of service to needy people",
        optionD: "all of the above",
        correct: "d",
    },
    {
        question: "The Nepal Engineers Association was established in",
        optionA: "2014 BS",
        optionB: "2024 BS",
        optionC: "2034 BS",
        optionD: "2044 BS",
        correct: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "The number of members in Nepal Engineers Association are",
        optionA: "5",
        optionB: "10",
        optionC: "15",
        optionD: "20",
        correct: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "The number of members in Nepal Engineering council are",
        optionA: "15",
        optionB: "18",
        optionC: "25",
        optionD: "28",
        correct: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "The number of members in NEC elected from NEA are",
        optionA: "2",
        optionB: "3",
        optionC: "4",
        optionD: "5",
        correct: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the tenure of NEC members?",
        optionA: "2 years",
        optionB: "3 years",
        optionC: "4 years",
        optionD: "5 years",
        correct: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the tenure of NEA members?",
        optionA: "2 years",
        optionB: "3 years",
        optionC: "4 years",
        optionD: "5 years",
        correct: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "As per the NEC Act 2055 the type of engineers are",
        optionA: "general, professional and foreigner",
        optionB: "special, local and international engineer",
        optionC: "civil, electrical and mechanical engineer",
        optionD: "computer, eletronics and agriculture engineer",
        correct: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "NEC Regulation 2057 is effective from",
        optionA: "2057/3/8",
        optionB: "2057/4/8",
        optionC: "2057/5/8",
        optionD: "2057/6/8",
        correct: "a"
    },

    {
        question: "Which one type of membership is not categorized by NEC?",
        optionA: "gengeral engineer",
        optionB: "foreign engineer",
        optionC: "professional engineer",
        optionD: "superintendent engineer",
        correct: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "For the registration of general engineer the amount of fee required is",
        optionA: "NRs 2000",
        optionB: "NRs 3000",
        optionC: "NRs 3500",
        optionD: "NRs 4000",
        correct: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "For the registiration of professional engineers the amount of fee required is",
        optionA: "NRS 5000",
        optionB: "NRS 10000",
        optionC: "NRS 15000",
        optionD: "NRS 20000",
        correct: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "For the registrationof foreginer engineers the amount of fee required is",
        optionA: "NRS 3000",
        optionB: "NRS 5000",
        optionC: "NRS 10000",
        optionD: "NRS 15000",
        correct: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "If the registration of an engineers is cancealed from NEC his name will be registerered or not if engineer is ready to register his name as per clause 18 NEC regulution",
        optionA: "yes",
        optionB: "no",
        optionC: "may be",
        optionD: "all of the above",
        correct: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "The minimum qualification required for a general engineer is",
        optionA: "diploma in engineering",
        optionB: "bachelor in engineering",
        optionC: "master in engineering ",
        optionD: "all of the above",
        correct: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "The minimum qualification required for a professional engineer is",
        optionA: "diploma in engineering",
        optionB: "bachelor in engineering",
        optionC: "master in engineering ",
        optionD: "all of the above",
        correct: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "The minimum qulification and experience required for the registration of foreigner engineers is",
        optionA: "bacheclor in engineering and 5 years exprerience",
        optionB: "bachelor in negineering and 10yrs experience",
        optionC: "master in engineering and 5 yrs experience",
        optionD: "master in engineering and 10yrs experience",
        correct: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "The registration book for general and professional engineers is written in Nepali language while for foreginer engineer in",
        optionA: "Nepali",
        optionB: "English",
        optionC: "Nepali and English",
        optionD: "French",
        correct: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "NEC publishes the name of registered engineers each year as well as every forth year. The name of foreigner engineers publish",
        optionA: "each year",
        optionB: "every forth year",
        optionC: "both (a) and (b)",
        optionD: "none of the above",
        correct: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "NEC act and its regulation are respectively",
        optionA: "55 and 57",
        optionB: "57 and 55",
        optionC: "55 and 56",
        optionD: "57 and 58",
        correct: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Nepal engineering council is an autonomous body formed under NEC act in",
        optionA: "2056 BS",
        optionB: "2055 BS",
        optionC: "2054 BS",
        optionD: "2053 BS",
        correct: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following category of Engineer is not mentioned in Engineering Council rule",
        optionA: "Charted Engineer",
        optionB: "General Engineer",
        optionC: "Professional Engineer",
        optionD: "Non-Nepali Regd. Engineer",
        correct: "a"
    },
    /* {
        question: "",
        optionA: "",
        optionB: "",
        optionC: "",
        optionD: "",
        correct: ""
    }, */



]
const Random = (data) => {
    const num = 3;
    const res = [];
    for (let i = 0; i < num;) {
        const random = Math.floor(Math.random() * data.length);
        if (res.indexOf(data[random]) !== -1) {
            continue;
        };
        res.push(data[random]);
        i++;
    };
    return res;
};
const estimatingProfessional = Random(dataProfessional)

export { dataProfessional, estimatingProfessional }